{
    "response_code": 0,
    "results": [
        {
            "category": "Entertainment: Film",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "Quanto fa 1+1?",
            "correct_answer": "2",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "3",
                "22",
                " 8"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "question": "Quanto fa 2+2?",
            "correct_answer": "4",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "2",
                "3",
                "1"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Science: Mathematics",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "question": "Quanto fa 3+3?",
            "correct_answer": "6",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "4",
                "2",
                "1"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Entertainment: Music",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "question": "Quanto fa 4+4?",
            "correct_answer": "8",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "99",
                "0",
                "5"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Geography",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "question": "Quanto fa 5+5?",
            "correct_answer": "10",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "9",
		"5",
		"4"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Entertainment: Music",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "question": "Quanto fa 6+6?",
            "correct_answer": "12",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "24",
                "3",
                "54"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Entertainment: Film",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "question": "Quanto fa 7+7?",
            "correct_answer": "14",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "44",
                "6",
                "7"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Science: Computers",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "question": "Quanto fa 8+8?",
            "correct_answer": "16",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "543",
                "100",
                "1240"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Sports",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "Quanto fa 9+9",
            "correct_answer": "18",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "300",
                "2566",
                "754"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "IQuanto fa 10+10?",
            "correct_answer": "20",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "4567",
                "0976",
                "23"
            ]
        }
    ]
}